<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<personnelRegistry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-00</employeeCode>
		<name>Hulk</name>
		<signatureDate>23-08-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>18.12.1966</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>0-</bloodType>
		<height>238cm</height>
		<weight>380kg</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Bruce Banner was born to Dr. Brian Banner and his wife Rebecca. Brian was an alcoholic father whose jealousy grew for Bruce as Rebecca shifted her focus from Brian to Bruce,Further, Brian believed that his radiation work had altered his DNA and given him a mutant son. Brian then abused Bruce and finally murdered Rebecca, then was placed in a mental hospital. After that, Bruce was raised by his aunt and father's sister, Susan Banner, who understood his great pain and rage over his childhood sufferings thanks to his crazed father, and raised him with love and care as if he were her own child.
 
Eventually when he became an adult he was a genius in nuclear physics, but without the proper funding, he was forced to go to the Desert State University. While performing a Gamma Bomb test until he saw a random civilian, so he asked his assistant Igor to stop the bomb, however because Igor was with the Soviet Union, he refused. Bruce was able to find a place to protect the bystander however he wasn't able to get back to his former location when the Gamma Bomb went off.
 
Somehow, Bruce survived the explosion thanks to a genetic factor in his body. This factor allowed Bruce to absorb the gamma radiation and after that night, he would frequently transform into the Green Goliath, also known as the Hulk.</background>
		<strengths>Gamma Radiation Physiology: Due to Bruce Banner being exposed to the Gamma Bomb's radiation culminating in his transformation into a powerful monster, The Incredible Hulk was for several times described as one of the physically most powerful beings in the entire Marvel Universe, with the potential for limitless levels of strength and durability (which scales directly with his strength). The Hulk, in the full exercise of his potential, was described as the most powerful regular humanoid, and his maximum known strength level ranges beyond the limits of virtually any other known humanoid being. The gamma radiation mutated his body and fortified his cellular structure, adding over 800 lbs of bone marrow and muscle tissues to his body. Additionally, during times of stress the Hulk's adrenaline level escalates, causing a corresponding escalation of brute strength. Thus, the madder Hulk gets, the stronger Hulk gets. Moreover, the Hulk was stated to be an Omega Level Threat by both the Initiative and Mister Fantastic, and even "the Original Omega Level Threat" by Gyrich. At one point, the Hulk was stated to be the strongest hero in the world.
 </strengths>
		<weaknesses>Gamma Radiation Draining: The Hulk is sometimes portrayed as vulnerable to gamma radiation draining by sufficiently powerful energy manipulators. Reverting to human form may be necessary for the Hulk to recharge his gamma energy. However, the Hulk is eventually characterized as possessing high degree of immunity to this weakness. For example, the mutant Darwin was unable to drain his gamma radiation, and Hulk deliberately transferred his energy into an entire race of absorbing entities without collapsing. Even previous to these events the Hulk has displayed this potential. For example, the hero Rom was unable to cure Banner from his condition, and the Hulk intentionally overloaded the Armageddon absorption mechanism.
 </weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-01</employeeCode>
		<name>DIO BRANDO</name>
		<signatureDate>12-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>1867-1868</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>MALE</sex>
		<bloodType>VAMPIRIC</bloodType>
		<height>1.95</height>
		<weight>105</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-02</employeeCode>
		<name>Gorilla Grodd</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>01.05.1959</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>0Neg</bloodType>
		<height>2</height>
		<weight>360</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Grodd is a hyper-intelligent telepathic gorilla able to control the minds of others. He was an average ape until an alien spacecraft (retconned from a radioactive meteor which also empowered Hector Hammond) crashed in Grodd's African home.[2] Grodd and his tribe of gorillas were imbued with super-intelligence by the ship's pilot. Grodd and fellow gorilla Solovar also developed telepathic and telekinetic powers. Led by the alien, the gorillas constructed the super-advanced Gorilla City.[3] The gorillas lived in peace until their home was discovered by explorers. Grodd forced one of the explorers to kill the alien and took over Gorilla City, planning to conquer the world next. Solovar telepathically contacted Barry Allen to warn of the evil gorilla's plans, and Grodd was defeated. The villain manages to return again and again to plague the Flash and the hero's allies.</background>
		<strengths>Grodd's psionic abilities allow him to place other beings under his mental control and transfer his consciousness into other bodies. Grodd also has (on occasion) vast telekinetic abilities ranging from force beams, telekinetic transmutation of matter and lifting thousands of tons mentally. he has shown the ability to absorb intelligence through the consumption of human brains. He possesses great superhuman strength far exceeding that of an ordinary gorilla. He is a scientific genius who has mastered Gorilla City's advanced technology and who has created many incredible inventions of his own. He also uses large laser guns.</strengths>
		<weaknesses>ains or strengthens his already vast psychokinetic abilities via ingesting a pill he develops after evolving himself into a human, enabling him to control the forces of nature. But after he turns back, he loses this power as his brain is not evolved enough</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-03</employeeCode>
		<name>Captain Cold</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>01.06.1957</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>0</bloodType>
		<height>187</height>
		<weight>87</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Leonard Snart was raised by an abusive father and took refuge with his grandfather, who worked in an ice truck. When his grandfather died, Snart grew tired of his father's abuse and set out to start a criminal career. Snart joined up with a group of small-time thieves and in planning out a robbery, each was issued a gun and a visor to protect their eyes against the flashes of gunfire. This visor design would later be adapted by Snart into his trademark costume. In recent years he has added a radio receiver to them which picks up the police band to monitor local law enforcement. Snart and the other thugs were captured by the Flash and imprisoned. Snart decided to go solo, but knew he had to do something about the local hero, the Flash.
Snart read an article that theorized that the energy emissions of a cyclotron could interfere with the Flash's speed. He designed a weapon to harness that power and broke into a cyclotron lab, intending to use the device to charge up his experimental gun. As he was finishing his experiment, a security guard surprised Snart. Intending to use his gun only to scare the guard, he inadvertently pulled the trigger and discovered that his weapon had been altered in a way he had never imagined. The moisture in the air around the guard froze. Intrigued by this twist of fate, Snart donned a parka and the aforementioned visor and declared himself to be Captain Cold - the man who mastered absolute zero.</background>
		<strengths>Like the majority of the Flash's Rogues, Snart had no innate superhuman powers. He instead relied on his cold guns and instincts. Fellow ice-based villain Mr Freezehas noted that Cold is the only cold-themed villain in the DC Universe to have mastered "absolute zero" with his weapons.
In the New 52 universe, Captain Cold temporarily had meta-human ice powers, including the power to slow down the Flash or objects traveling at high velocities via molecular deceleration caused by Absolute Zero, but these powers are later lost in the Forever evil series when he is attacked by Deathstorm—the Earth-3 counterpart of Firestorm—with Cold reverting to using his classic ice gun. Despite his lack of professional or technical expertise, Cold states that he spent so long analyzing the parts of his cold gun that he is able to recreate it in just over half an hour using parts stolen from a standard electronics shop. He's even skilled enough to program it for a host of unique effects simulating some of his powers; like his "Cold Field" which quick cools the atmosphere to the point that everything caught in it grinds to a halt,or an auto activation function which triggers his Cold Gun's freeze ray via vocalized password input.
During the Rebirth storyline, Snart augmented his Cold Gun even further by combining it with the anti-Speed Force technologies by the science criminal cell called Black Hole.The newly christened Black Ice Gun now tacked directly into The Speed Force in order to painfully disrupt a speedster's connection to it. Snart's new cold gun was so powerful that not only could it hinder the Flash in the most excruciating way possible, it was vastly more powerful in scope, able to freeze both the harbor and several city blocks adjacent to their current location.
</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Looking for a way out for him and his sister, Leonard did what so many youths with no other options do; he turned to crime. Leonard started off with small jobs - stealing cars and sticking up gas stations - but as he got better at the work, he moved up. Working with local gangs, Leonard started to go after bigger jobs, including banks and jewelry stores. Through it all, Leonard kept to his second rule and never hit or attacked anyone he was robbing, which often led to him getting into arguments with his fellow criminals. After Flash returned from the Flashpoint, the world was different, and that included The Rogues. In this reality, they had never killed a Flash, but they were still darker than they had been before. Captain Cold's "no killing" rule was replaced with "no killing unless..." which opened the door for The Rogues to go further than ever before. Captain Cold's rage about his father was eating him up inside, and the constant losses to Flash weren't helping. When the chance presented itself, Leonard used his fellow Rogues to take over Central City with the help of Perpetua and Lex Luthor. With the help of Golden Glider, Flash defeated Captain Cold but not before hundreds of Central City citizens were killed.</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-04</employeeCode>
		<name>Homelander</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>4.7.1981</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>-</bloodType>
		<height>1,8</height>
		<weight>75</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>America's first and greatest superhero, and an unknown egg donor. Raised in a lab, he was surrounded by doctors like Jonah Vogelbaum, who named him John. For not having a real family, Vogelbaum remarked that John turned violent, aggressive, and downright hateful ("The Self-Preservation Society"). Throughout his childhood, "John" was put through painful physical experiments and surgeries to test the true limits of his abilities. Some of these tests included having his hand forced into a furnace while he cried, being boiled alive, and being forced to fight strength-enhanced Vought guards("One Plus One Equals Two"). He was also put under strict mental brainwashing and was forced to spend hours sitting in front of a projector that displayed images that were chosen to mold his personality, such as the American flag, Jesus Christ, and baseball. </background>
		<strengths>Superhuman strength, speed, stamina, durability, smell, and hearing
Poison and Toxin Immunity
Regenerative Healing Factor
Invulnerability
Heat vision
X-Ray vision
Flight</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Mentally unstable
Carelessness
Insecure
Cannot see through zinc
High frequencies
</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-05</employeeCode>
		<name>Penguin</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>26.06.1970</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>AB+</bloodType>
		<height>1.47</height>
		<weight>110</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Born Oswald Chesterfield Cobblepot, the Penguin was teased very much in his childhood due to his short stature, obesity, and bird-like nose. These traits made him an outcast in his rich, debutante family. Their rejection drove him to become evil.</background>
		<strengths>	•	Genius-Level Intellect: From an early age Penguin was never very physically strong (despite being a skilled martial artist) or appealing and this forced him to learn to live life with a keen intellect. It should be noted that his intellect is almost always sinister in nature even in the most mundane of decisions.
		Business Management: Oswald's criminal operations would succeed without a hitch if not for the actions of Batman. Oswald has existed both above and below the law with his businesses; running a legitimate night club as well as selling drugs and weapons from within it.
		Leadership: Penguin always travels with henchmen on any criminal mission or even to outings. He controls bodyguards, chefs, servants, gang members, villains, and so on with masterful talent. He often likes to be with beautiful women to compensate for his grotesque appearance. Oswald has led both legal and illegal operations within Gotham City; under any conditions, such as the Iceberg Lounge.
		Cold Tolerance: The Penguin can tolerate sub-freezing temperatures longer than most people. He can spend extended times outdoors in the winter before frostbite, hypothermia, or even discomfort begin. This ability is not superhuman; he is just at the far end of normal human cold tolerance due to his obesity.
</strengths>
		<weaknesses>The Penguin was addicted to tobacco, which he constantly smoked out of a cigarette in a cigarette holder.</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-06</employeeCode>
		<name>Doctor Doom</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>6.9.1969</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>O</bloodType>
		<height>187</height>
		<weight>102</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Dr. Victor von Doom, Ph.D a.k.a. Doctor Doom is a Latverian politician who serves as the Monarch and Supreme Leader for the Kingdom of Latveria. He was scarred from an accident and wears an iron mask and armor to hide his true face. He is considered one of the most brilliant minds and scientists on the planet Earth. He is also a sorcerer with skills in magic matching the most powerful beings in the Universe, making him a potential candidate for Sorcerer Supreme. He hopes to bring order and betterment to humanity through world conquest. Unequalled in ability, ego, and will power, he has come into conflict with both superhumans and cosmic beings. He is best known as the rival of Reed Richards and archenemy of the Fantastic Four.</background>
		<strengths>Super-Genius Intelligence: Doctor Doom's most dangerous weapon is his intellect. He is one of the top mortal minds on the planet. Doom even cured Ben Grimm of his Thing form. Doom has constructed hundreds of devices, including a working time machine, devices which can imbue people with powers and many types of robots.His most frequently used robots are his "Doombots," exact mechanical replicas of himself. They look like him, talk like him, and even act like him. Individually, Doombots have an advanced AI (artificial intelligence) so that each one believes itself to be the real Doom. As a safety measure, each Doombot has a dampener program that is triggered whenever the real Doom (or another Doombot) is nearby. These "body doubles" appear when Doom cannot be present or is unwilling to risk his own life, and are often responsible for Doom's seeming return from certain death. Another common type of robot used is the Servo-Guard, the police force of Latveria. Doom specializes in all levels of physics, robotics, cybernetics, genetics, materials science, weapons technology, biochemistry, and time travel. He also has natural talents for leadership, strategy, politics, and manipulation. He has been shown as a prodigious electrical and mechanical engineer, admired by Tony Stark, an inspired theoretician with extensive knowledge of parallel universes and dimensions,[citation needed] and even a practiced neurosurgeon, having surgically separated Hulk from Bruce Banner. His knowledge extents to virtually any scientific field and his mind is said to work as fast as a sophisticated computer.</strengths>
		<weaknesses>It has been shown in the past that Doom can be manipulated by pandering to his sense of superiority, especially over Reed Richards. Spider-Man was able to gain his assistance concerning unknown technology by saying Reed could not figure it out. This ego is also the main reason for his vendetta against Reed, as he cannot accept that Reed understood his equations better than he did. </weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-07</employeeCode>
		<name>Hobgoblin</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>13.11.1964</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>B+</bloodType>
		<height>01-08-2022</height>
		<weight>83,91</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Roderick Kingsley was a successful fashion designer and millionaire who had built his empire through underworld ties and unethical practices. One of his criminal associates, George Hill, had stumbled upon one of the secret lairs of the original Green Goblin. He relayed this information to Kingsley, who killed him to ensure the secret would remain hidden. 

Reading through Norman Osborn's journals and examining the various "goblin" paraphernalia and weaponry, Kingsley found himself enthralled with the idea of becoming a costumed criminal. Therefore he forged a new identity, with an altered costume as the Hobgoblin.</background>
		<strengths>Good fashion sense. Can also make a killer GT. (Literally... it will kill you.)</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Is always defeted by Spiderman and is unable to get along with the Green Goblin.</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-08</employeeCode>
		<name>Dr.Light</name>
		<signatureDate>10-03-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>26.07.2002</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<height>1,81</height>
		<weight>84</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>I am born in Finland but have lived in Sweden for hole my life. I live in Mariehamn right now.</background>
		<strengths>disciplined, hard worker and good listener.</strengths>
		<weaknesses>can be a bit silent sometimes but not a weakness I would say.</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-09</employeeCode>
		<name>Ganondorf</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>15.11.1987</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>B</bloodType>
		<height>2,3</height>
		<weight>132</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Ganon is the main antagonist in The Legend of Zelda series and is presented as the embodiment of evil. He usually appears as the final boss at the end of each game. A recurring storyline in the series centres around the protagonist Link fighting to save Princess Zelda after she is captured by Ganon. Over the course of the series, Ganon has been depicted in various physical forms. As the human form known as Ganondorf, he is the king and the only male member of the Gerudo. He bears the physical traits of the Gerudo race, having red hair, dark skin and pointy ears. He also often transforms into a monstrous beast resembling a giant boar with glowing eyes. Ganon has been given various titles over the series, including "King of Evil", "King of Thieves", "the Dark Lord", "King of Darkness" and "Prince of Darkness".</background>
		<strengths>big and strong</strengths>
		<weaknesses>a little silly</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-10</employeeCode>
		<name>Metroid Prime</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>18.10.1998</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>0</bloodType>
		<height>02-05-2022</height>
		<weight>200</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Prime was born after a Metroid absorbed large amounts of Phazon energy from the Phazon Core. The Metroid was corrupted and became the Guardian of the Leviathan Seed that struck Tallon IV 50 years before the events of the game. However, it is unknown how a Metroid got inside the Impact Crater before Samus released the Cipher.</background>
		<strengths>The aberration known as Metroid Prime is the source of Phazon, making it immensely powerful. 
Only its head is truly vulnerable: other attacks are a nuisance. 

Offensively, Metroid Prime has a number of natural and mechanical weapons at its desposal. These include Ultrafrigid Breath, Multi-Missiles, Snare Beams, and Partical Wave Projectors. Its massive strength and barbed carapace make it lethal in melee combat. Recommend maximum firepower when engaging this enemy.</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Follows the same pattern over and over again.
A genetic flaw makes it susceptible to certain weapoms for brief periods. </weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-11</employeeCode>
		<name>Harley Quinn</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>10.10.1992</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>F</sex>
		<bloodType>A+</bloodType>
		<height>1,55</height>
		<weight>59</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Harleen Quinzel was a psychiatrist at Arkham Asylum, and after meeting the Joker, she became his frequent accomplice, takes on the name Harley Quinn, and gets in an abusive codependent relationship with him. She eventually splits up with him, and becomes a solo criminal, forming a criminal gang called the Quinntets. </background>
		<strengths>unpredictability, gymnastics skills, and weapons and hand-to-hand proficiency.[99] She is a peak athlete, having won a gymnastics scholarship at Gotham City's Gotham State University. Following her transition to main DC canon in 1999, Harley Quinn was established as having immunity to toxins and enhanced strength, agility, durability, and reflexes, which she received after having been injected a serum concocted by Poison Ivy. "Vengeance Unlimited, Part Five" (Harley Quinn vol. 1 #30) revealed that it also gave her the ability to breathe underwater. Despite being mentally unstable and sometimes distracted, Harley is highly intelligent</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Harley Quinn has no superpowers. She is mentally unstable and does not have particular strategic or scientific skills.</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-12</employeeCode>
		<name>Yoshikage Kira</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>30.01.1966</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>A</bloodType>
		<height>01-08-2022</height>
		<weight>64</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<strengths> Killer Queen, Sheer Heart Attack, Bites the Dust, Stray Cat (kind of?), Hayato~...</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Sheer Heart Attack has no weaknesses.</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-13</employeeCode>
		<name>Shredder</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>15.4.1967</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>-</sex>
		<bloodType>-</bloodType>
		<height>1,9</height>
		<weight>95</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Little is known about the Shredder's history except that he was born on April 15, 1967. he actually raised Eric Sacks in Japan after Sacks' father died in Vietnam War and he is such a skilled and ruthless warrior.</background>
		<strengths>Immense Strength, Immense Speed,Robotic Samurai Armour</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Clumsy and slow</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-14</employeeCode>
		<name>Megatron</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>01.09.1984</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>A</bloodType>
		<height>9.14</height>
		<weight>36000</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Leader of the Decepticons</background>
		<strengths>Evil</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Optimus Prime</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-15</employeeCode>
		<name>Kent Agent</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>1.1.1900</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>A</bloodType>
		<height>2</height>
		<weight>250</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Top secret</background>
		<strengths>Everything</strengths>
		<weaknesses>None</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-17</employeeCode>
		<name>Burebista</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2021</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>06061590</dateOfBirth>
		<bloodType>A2</bloodType>
		<height>1.63</height>
		<weight>60</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>I Burebista am an impressive political and military leader of the lands inhabited by the Dacian ghettos.
I came to the head of my people, who were exhausted by frequent wars, I the Geth Burebista raised the state so much by exercises, abstinence from wine and obedience to the commandments, that in a few years he made a powerful state and subjected the Geths to the most most of the neighboring populations, coming to be feared even by the Romans.
Being a perfect leader and military strategist I succeeded in uniting the Geto-Dacian tribes, and with the help of my advice as a tarabostes and with the help of the high priest, Deceneus, I managed to introduce a series of administrative measures that have an important role in the consolidation and stability of the state, I recruited new people for the administration of agriculture, the collection of donations, the supervision of compulsory public works, thus making possible the realization of the system of fortifications in Dacia, I introduced the system of Beliginese laws, and on the spiritual level I strengthened my own cult.

</background>
		<strengths> I am endowed with remarkable qualities as an organizer, military strategist and diplomat, I have a solid and balanced character. I am a robust man, with very good physical condition, being a fighter and a traveler.
</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Emotional.</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-18</employeeCode>
		<name>Thanos</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>14.10.1953</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>unspecified</bloodType>
		<height>201</height>
		<weight>448</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Thanos was born on Saturn's moon Titan as the son of Eternals A'lars and Sui-San, the nephew of Zuras, and the grandnephew of Uranos. His brother is Eros of Titan. Thanos carries the Deviants gene, and as such, shares the physical appearance of the Eternals' cousin race. Shocked by his appearance and the belief that he would destroy all life in the universe, Sui-San went insane and attempted to kill him, but she was stopped by A'lars. During his school years, Thanos was a pacifist and would only play with his brother Eros and pets. By adolescence, Thanos had become fascinated with nihilism and entropy, worshipping and eventually falling in love with the physical embodiment of Mistress Death. As an adult, Thanos augmented his physical strength and powers through his superior scientific knowledge using a combination of mysticism and cybernetic enhancements. He also attempted to create a new life for himself by siring many children as well as becoming a pirate. He finds no fulfillment in either until he is visited again by Mistress Death, for whom he murders his offspring and his pirate captain.</background>
		<strengths>- Thanos is Immortal (and a very old being) and is impossible to kill.
- Thanos possesses Superhuman Durability: It is proven by the fact that he can touch and wield the Infinity Stones without getting injured.
- His sword is made of the metal Uru, one of the strongest metals in the Marvel Universe.
- Comic Thanos is the smartest and the strongest character other than the Gods in the universe. Even without the stones, Avengers combined can beat him only because he subconsciously beats himself.
- has the infinity gauntlet</strengths>
		<weaknesses>- his single most terrible weakness to be: his pride</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-19</employeeCode>
		<name>Joker</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>21.11.1946</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>O-</bloodType>
		<height>1,95</height>
		<weight>87</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Arthur was an amateur stand-up comedian and a professional clown. He lost his job as a clown after being framed by a co-worker. He was later repeatedly assaulted by various people and unsuccessfully tried to resurrect his career.

Arthur also lost access to his medication and therapist, causing him to succumb to madness as he killed his deceitful mother and took on the identity of the Joker.</background>
		<strengths>The Joker possesses no superhuman abilities, instead using his expertise in chemical engineering to develop poisonous or lethal concoctions and thematic weaponry, including razor-tipped playing cards, deadly joy buzzers, and acid-spraying lapel flowers</strengths>
		<weaknesses>My ego.</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-20</employeeCode>
		<name>Red Skull</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>1985</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>AB+</bloodType>
		<height>1,8</height>
		<weight>130</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Born in Finland.
Studied pharmacy and medical.</background>
		<strengths>Is creative and can come up with ideas and solutions to problems.</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Cant focus on many things at once.</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-21</employeeCode>
		<name>Voldemort</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>31.12.1926</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>0</bloodType>
		<height>1.90</height>
		<weight>81</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>Previously know as Tom Marvolo Riddle. He became the dark lord to take control of the Wizarding world by manipulating the festering relationship between pureblood and Muggle-born wizards.

Voldemort is the archenemy of Harry Potter, who according to a prophecy has "the power to vanquish the Dark Lord". He attempts to murder the boy, but instead kills his parents, Lily and James Potter, and leaves Harry with a scar on his forehead in the shape of a lightning bolt. Nearly every witch or wizard dares not utter his name and refers to him instead with such monikers as "You-Know-Who", "He Who Must Not Be Named", or "the Dark Lord".

Voldemort's obsession with blood purity signifies his aim to rid the wizarding world of Muggle (non-magical) heritage and to conquer both worlds, Muggle and wizarding, to achieve pure-blood dominance. Through his mother's family, he is the last descendant of the wizard Salazar Slytherin, one of the four founders of Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. He is the leader of the Death Eaters, a group of evil wizards and witches dedicated to ridding the Wizarding World of Muggles and establishing Voldemort as its supreme ruler.</background>
		<strengths>Voldemort is an extremely powerful wizard. He knows a lot of spells and is especially proficient in the Dark Arts. He learns new concepts easily.

In spite of his narcissism, Voldemort can acknowledge his mistakes and displays a degree of calculated humility. He did not hastily announce his return of power as soon as he regained his physical form except to his supporters and with his candor and charm, winning him his followers and sought to make hay of his missteps, openly revealing such unflattering information to his followers and using it to illustrate how he could use his wits to further enhance his powers. He also showed his followers leniency, even though they had not sought to help him after his downfall, realizing he could not afford to mistreat them until returning to full strength.
</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Voldemort has an arrogant personality and is insensitive to other people's feelings. He has a total disregard for things that he does not understand and has a weak sense of smell.

Voldemort is a xenophobe, despising non-magical humans ("Muggles") and those who are of mixed magical and Muggle heritage, even though he is one of the latter himself.</weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-22</employeeCode>
		<name>William Stryker</name>
		<signatureDate>03-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>05.02.1955</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>O-</bloodType>
		<height>1,83</height>
		<weight>82</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>William Stryker was a Catholic Priest who, after discovering the existence of mutants, grew to hate and fear them, but he also saw the potential they possessed. His radical views about mutants eventually got him excommunicated from the church, so he decided to fall back on his military background. </background>
		<strengths>Stryker has been converted into a cyborg, equipped with adamantium parts. His adamantium construction gives him a high level of superhuman durability, enabling him to survive being grievously wounded by H-Alpha, though he was unable to move.</strengths>
		<weaknesses>Over the years, he found himself involved in a shady organization called Weapon X, which was dedicated to the recruitment and weaponization of mutants. Eventually, Stryker found himself leading a squad of a handful of deadly mutants, including Wolverine, Sabretooth, Omega Red, and Deadpool. </weaknesses>
	</employee>
	<employee>
		<employeeCode>IT21-23</employeeCode>
		<name>Boba Fett</name>
		<signatureDate>12-10-2022</signatureDate>
		<dateOfBirth>19.04.1971</dateOfBirth>
		<sex>M</sex>
		<bloodType>O+</bloodType>
		<height>1.83</height>
		<weight>80</weight>
		<rank>Junior Data Analyst</rank>
		<securityAccessLevel>C</securityAccessLevel>
		<department>Medical Data Department</department>
		<background>He's a renowned mandalorian bounty hunter whose career stretched from the from the fall of the Galatic Republic till the end of the era of the Galactic Empires rule. He pilots the Slave I, his starship that originally belonged to his father and genetic donor Jango Fett, hence Boba is actually a clone.
</background>
		<strengths>Trained in comabt and martial arts, a skilled marksman with a was assortment of equipment including his main rifle balster, a jetpack and miniature flamethrower on his wrist. He also has vasta array of other blasters and grenades and a crossbow. His armor also is very durable. 
</strengths>
		<weaknesses>He doesn't have a great record when it comes to the Sarlacc's pit.
</weaknesses>
	</employee>
</personnelRegistry>